(Sheldon:)...were starting to say I was a witch.
(Alex:)Sheldon thinks the approach
in his paper might change the way...
(Alex:)...we calculate ferromagnetic hysteresis.
- Oh. It's about time. I hated the old way.
(Penny:)- Hi, I'm Penny.
- Alex.
(Alex:)- Do you work with Dr. Hofstadter?
- In a way.
(Penny:)We've kind of been involved
in a five-year experiment.
(Alex:)Oh. Well, you're lucky.
He seems very talented.
(Alex:)I'm sure a lot of people
wanna work with him.
Oh, well, a lot of people can't, so...
Uh, come on.
(Leonard:)Where are we going?
(Penny:)My limbic system
wants to take your pants off.
(Leonard:)She seems nice.
(Sheldon:)Notice people on your own time.
We're working.
(Bernadette:)Hey, Howie, how you feeling?
(Howard:)Better. Much better.
(Howard:)The other astronauts held me down
and gave me a shot.
(Alex:)Ooh.
(Howard:)Attention, people of Earth.
(Howard:)Tonight there will be two moons
in the sky.
(Bernadette:)Howie, stop that.
(Bernadette:)NASA's watching this.
(Bernadette:)Put your pants back on.
(Howard:)Whee!